Sara Hailu Gebre

■ sarahhailu2010@gmail.com 🔲 +251949446044

in/sara-hailu-690765232?utm_source=share&utm_campaign=share_via&utm_content=profile&utm_medium=android_app

SUMMARY

A Full Stack Web Developer skilled in building and maintaining web applications using the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js). Experienced in JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and Python, with experience in MySQL and MongoDB. Familiar with developing APIs, version control using Git.

EXPERIENCE

website Developer

Everlink Digital Technologies

June 2023 - August 2023, Addis Abeba, Ethiopia

• At Everlink Tech, I embarked on developing a comprehensive learning management system (LMS) using the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js). The project started as an idea to facilitate online course creation, student enrollment, and progress tracking, aiming to provide a robust platform for educators and learners.

website developer

oli system

July 2022 - August 2022, Addis abeba, Ethiopia

PROJECTS

EHR

For semester Project · April 2023 - May 2024

 a blockchain-based electronic health recording system mainly aimed at seamless data sharing between different authorized healthcare centers in order to enhance the delivery of health care services.

LMS

Everlink · July 2023 - August 2023

· This project aimed to facilitate online course creation, student enrollment, and progress tracking.

EDUCATION

Bachelors Degree in computer Science and engineering

Adama Science and Technology university, Adama \cdot Adama , Ethiopia \cdot 2024 \cdot 3.26

CERTIFICATIONS

Dereja Academy Accelerator Program

At our University • 2024

 $\cdot \text{ I am certified in Self-discovery, communication, Effective planning, project management, and other professional skills to develop some soft skills.}$

ALX, Software Engineering

online • 2023

 \cdot I am certified for a 12-month ALX Software Engineering course in Backend -specialization

SKILLS

Frontend:

· HTML/CSS,React.js, Bootstrap

Backend:

· Node.js, Express.js, PHP

Database Management:

· MongoDB, MySQL

Version Control:

· Git, GitHub